We have arrived(到达) at the dawn(黎明) of a new era.
We will face the unknown together.
I don't know what it is,
but there's plenty of people out here trying(尝试) to figure it out.
You know I've(我不知道) got your back.
Damn(该死) well better, I'm your captain.
We have to work together.
For the good of the new Belter state.
Detective Miller(米勒) crashed(崩溃) into Venus(金星).
I'm just an investigator(调查员) now.
I find things.
Couple hundred billion brain cells(细胞) in your skull.
When I push a few trillion(万亿) of them buttons(按钮)
in exactly the right way, you're talking(说话) to Miller.
Miller(米勒) showed(显示) me things.
A whole civilization.
They made(创造) the station, this space.
Something killed(杀死) them. They tried(尝试) to stop it.
Burned(烧焦了) whole solar systems.
Only, it didn't work.
When we detonated(引爆) our bomb,
I believe we became(成为) the threat.
We taught(教) the station that our ships(船舶) are fusion(聚变) bombs.
We need to shut down every reactor(反应堆) in the flotilla(舰队).
That station is gonna(要) wipe us all out,
unless we make this happen now.
Together till the end?
We're on the brink(边缘) right now
because we keep reacting(反应) to things(事情) we don't understand!
And we're reaching(达到) for violence
because we can't figure out what to do.
Don't shoot!
Fuck.
You've given us a new frontier,
1,300 habitable(可居住) systems(系统) on the other side of those rings.
It's gonna(要) be another blood-soaked gold rush.
The civilization(文明) that built(建造) the rings(戒指) is gone, wiped(擦) out.
What could have killed(杀死) them?
That's(没错) what I'd like to know.
Gonna need a ride.
Unidentified(身份不明) Belter ships,
you are entering(进入) restricted(限制) space.
Veer(转向) off now, or we will fire!
Barbapiccola, this is the UNN(联合国新闻网) Tripoli.
Shut down your drive now, or we will fire.
Respond immediately.
We are unarmed. This is a refugee ship.
Mama, I'm scared.
Whatever happens, we will be together.
Together.
Tripoli, you are not authorized(授权的) to fire inside the Ring Space.
Barbapiccola, the OPA orders(命令) you to comply.
We will not.
We've(我们已经) been(一直) begging(乞求) for a port since Ganymede(木卫三) fell.
No one would let us land.
If you're going to kill us,
just do it now, or let us go!
Go.
Go! Go! Go!
Now, that's(没错) a good cup of coffee.
Did you speak to Naomi?
It was lovely meeting her,
except it was through a screen.
It's such a shame she couldn't(不能) come down and see the farm.
Mom...
That was a long trip you were on.
She could have taken(采取) those gravity(重力) drugs(药物) on the way.
It's not that easy.
Those drugs(毒品) are brutal.
I wouldn't(不会) have asked(问) her to do that for me.(我。)
And this isn't(不是) her home.
Most Belters have mixed(混合的) feelings(感情) about Earth.
Here.
It's for your next long haul.
Think I need to reread(重读) this?
What did you see out there?
It's hard to put into words.
Storm's coming.
I'm gonna(要) go close up the house.
I'll be right in.(在。)
Gonna be a real turd-floater, huh?
Perfect words(文字) for every occasion.
We gotta(得走了) talk about that ride.
The ride? Yeah, I know.
Next clue(线索) to the case.
We're leaving(离开) tomorrow.
Are(是吗) we going to the Ring?
We're going to New York.
What the hell's in New York?
Tall buildings, good pizza,
Secretary-General(秘书长,) of the United Nations,
- who summoned(召唤) me.(我。) - So you can ask her,
tell her to let you go through the Ring.
I have, a hundred times.
I'll bring it up again,
but something must have changed(变化) if she wants(想要) to talk.
We gotta(得走了) talk about that ride, kid.
Next clue(线索) to the case.
I wonder what that rain tastes(味道) like.
I used to love the rain when I was a kid.
I'd sit out here and watch the lightning(闪电) storms.
Sounds(声音) beautiful.
We gotta(得走了) talk about that ride, kid.
Next clue(线索) to the case.
You got it, Miller. I'll take care of it.
I hope we get a chance to meet in person one day.
You know, I'm quite a dancer.
Holden(霍尔顿) never stops(停止) saying.
Fong(方先生) kopenga tolwanda ert(电化学反应堆) el(埃尔) Belte
fong(方) kopenga tolowabda Ert.
Okay, okay, okay.
Bye, now. Bye!
Bye-bye!(再见) Bye! Take care!
That was agonizing.
Yes, it was.
I'll see you soon.
Love you.
New railgun's looking(看) good.
I just need you to check out the thrust(推力) compensator(补偿器).
If thing's not tied(并列) into our drive just right,
we're all gonna(要) get tossed(投掷) into the ceiling(天花板) every time it fires(开火).
I'm on it.
Hey, Amos.
Melba?
Please, Clarissa.
I get one vid(视频) message a month now.
I...
didn't have anyone to call.
- Okay. - So you coming(来了) down the well?
Nope.
Not even to feel the surf(海浪) through your toes?
There's(有的) a lot of past in my past.(过去。)
I'm gonna(要) skip(跳过) it.
At least you have the choice.
I'm gonna(要) spend the rest of my life in here.
Like Dad.
Yeah, they really threw(扔) the book at you.
I called(叫) to say thank you.
For what?(什么？)
The months(月) heading(航向) home,
letting(让) me work in the shop with you,
- it kept(保持) me sane. - You're a good mechanic.
I've(我不知道) been(一直) thinking about something.
Remember when you sent(发送) me to check on the...
the seals(封印) in the air lock?
Yep.
The safeties(安全) had been(一直) overridden, and...
if I wanted(需要) to, I could have blown(吹) the outer(外部的) door
while I was in it, killed(杀死) myself.
Yep.
Was(曾经是) that on purpose?
If I was staring(凝视) down a lifetime sentence,
I'd want to have the option.
It was kind of you to make the offer.
But Anna was right. I...
- I don't deserve the easy way out. - Stop it.
You breathe in, you breathe out,
eat, shit, sleep,
you take whatever they give you,
and you give nothing in return.
I have to go.
They have me doing dream therapy.
I don't really understand it, but...
the doctor has flowers(花) in her office,
and I can smell them through the glass.
Good luck with that.
Can I bother you again sometime?
Sure thing, Peaches.
What I want is more ships(船舶) at the Ring blockade.
All I need from you is to make that happen.
Our assets(资产) in the outer(在外) planets(行星) have been(一直) decimated.
We don't have the ships.
We could redeploy(重新部署) elements(元素) of the Home Fleet.
You forgot(忘记) about Mars?
It's a new day. We're all friends(朋友) now.
Madam(女士) Secretary, if I may...
Nancy, don't start this shit(该死) with me again.
Half our population is unemployed(失业),
and we've(我们已经) been(一直) given the biggest(最大的) opportunity(机会)
to give them jobs, to give them a purpose in a century.
Every week, another colony(殖民地) ship filled(装满) with our constituents(选民)
shows(显示) up at the blockade, and we make them wait.
They're(他们是) sitting(坐) ducks(鸭子) for pirates(海盗).
They want to explore new worlds.
We should let them.
When Columbus(哥伦布) arrived,
at least he knew(知道) what was waving(挥手) at him was human.
We've(我们已经) sent(发送) out hundreds(数百) of probes(探测器) through the Rings.
Not one of them has turned(转动) up any little green men.
You haven't seen(看到) it yet, so it doesn't exist.
That's(没错) your argument?
You can't control a goddamn(该死的) gold rush.
When the stacks(堆) of body bags(袋) came(来) back from the Yukon,
thousands(数千) of hopeful(希望的) idiots(白痴)
lined(衬里) up to be the next corpses.
The only reason there weren't any riots(暴乱) in the streets(街道)
when we fired(解雇) on the Ganymede(木卫三) ships(船舶)
was because they were Belters.
Sooner(更快) or later, an Earth ship will try to run the blockade.
Are(是吗) you going to shoot down our own citizens,
or are we gonna(要) turn this situation to our advantage?
We are going to do what I goddamn(该死的) said(说)
we are going to do...
So do it.
Are(是吗) you familiar with the Barbapiccola?
Refugee ship from Ganymede(木卫三).
One of the four that slipped(滑倒) through the Ring
before the blockade(封锁) went up.
They were never heard(听到) from again.
We heard(听到) from them again.
The Belters have been(一直) installing(安装) comm relays(通信中继器)
through the Ring gates,
prioritizing(优先) those four systems.
The relays(继电器) went live two days(日) ago
and started(开始) picking(采摘) up broadcasts(广播) from one system.
By some miracle,
the Belters on this world survived.
About a hundred or so.
They're calling(呼叫) the planet Ilus.
Makes(制造) sense.
Ilus was a brother of Ganymede(木卫三).
Who gives(给) a fuck?
I didn't bring you here to teach me mythology(神话学).
The planet is practically(实际上) made(成的) of lithium(锂).
They're mining(采矿) it.
Belters struck(击中) it rich. Good for them.
They also found this.
That looks(看) like the work of the protomolecule.
Doesn't appear to be active.
And for a few hundred years, we thought
Phoebe(菲比) was just a ball of ice orbiting(轨道) Saturn(土星).
I want you to go to Ilus.
Are(是吗) you still talking(说话) to Miller?
It's more like he talks(会谈) to me.(我。)
You said(说) the worlds(世界) on the other side
of those Rings(戒指) were killed...
genocide(种族灭绝) on a scale
that we cannot(无法) even begin to comprehend(理解).
You have the insight to the protomolecule
that no one else does.
I need to know what is really going on over there.
Is Ilus a ghost(鬼魂) town
or another fucking Eros?
And if it is another Eros?
Evacuate(撤离) the Belters,
destroy the protomolecule if you can,
and get the hell out of there.
Nice of Avasarala to clear up our salvage(打捞) claim.
- How'd she look? - Fine.
No, I mean, like,
what was she wearing?
It's good to be home.
Avasarala's worried it could become another Eros.
If Miller's right, it could be something much worse.
She already has a ship en route,
the Edward Israel.
It's a science ship, survey vessel out of Titan.
A warship's more her style. That's(没错) for sure.
It's not a military operation.
They've got the gear and the expertise(知识) to assess the situation
and hopefully(希望) contain any contamination(污染).
We'll have access to their resources(资源) if we need them.
Look, I opened(打开) those gates.
So I'm responsible(负责)
if anything comes(来) through them.
We all opened(打开) those gates.
All right.
At Ilus,
Amos and I will transfer to the Edward Israel
and take their shuttle(穿梭机) down to the surface.
Naomi, you and Alex(亚历克斯) will stay in orbit(轨道) on the Roci...
I'm going to the surface too.
Are(是吗) you sure?
It's a long trip to Ilus.
I'll(我会) have time to prepare.
There's(有的) 1,300 new systems(系统) out there,
and I don't want to see them all from orbit.
All right, then, in which case,
we're gonna(要) need to rig(钻机) the Roci for an unassisted(助的) landing(着陆).
- I know a guy on Luna. - Give him a call.
So this guy does MCRN retrofits(加装)?
Uh-huh, works cheap and fast, doesn't ask questions.
Naomi...
Whatever happens(发生) down there,
we'll deal with it together.
Arriving(到了) at Innis(女名女子名) Shallows(浅滩) Station.
Stand clear of the doors.
Civilian Accountability(问责制) Committee
reminds(提醒) all citizens(市民) that your quarterly(季度) action report
is due in two weeks.
The assistance desk is open for 24 hours(小时) and 2/3
for your questions(问题) and concerns.
Don't miss your deadline.
Mars(火星) is better for everyone when everyone does(工作) their part.
Bobbie.
See you, Rana.
Hey, I got a few bites(咬) on apartments,
so I shouldn't(应该) be too much longer.
As long as you need, Bobbie.
I'm gonna(要) shower(淋浴) and head out for a pop.
Keep an eye out for David?
Sure.
Hey, sit down. Stay a while.
Can't. Got a study date.
Huh. Pretty good. Thank you.
Yeah, I can really heat 'em up.
Shit, she's(她是) early.
Hey, Leelee. Let me get my stuff.
Hey?
You're Aunt Bobbie.
David talks(会谈) about you all the time.
He says(说) you're a war hero.
He's(他是) a sweet kid.
Uh, you ready?
It's nice to meet you.
Hey, Bobbie.
Nice to see you, flyboy.
I'm just passing(传递) through the neighborhood(邻居),
thought I'd check in live for a change.
How you doing?
- Getting(获得) by. - Oh, yeah?
I saw(锯) the news you're heading(航向) to the Ring.
Are(是吗) you going to New Terra?
I can neither confirm nor deny that.
There's(有的) protomolecule down there.
Yeah, so it would appear.
Apparently(显然) we are experts(专家) in the field,
so who better to go and see for sure, right?
And how are you feeling about it?
You wouldn't(不会) understand.
What's(什么事) that supposed to mean?
You've never been(一直) scared(害怕) of anything in your life.
Sure, I have. All the time.
But there's a trick.
You just have to believe
that what you're doing really matters,
and then the fear can't control you.
Oh, shit. Delay's getting(得到) bad.
Shit.
Take care of yourself, flyboy.
You too, Bobbie.
UN freighter Amberjack,
we got you target lock.
Give us cargo. We no fight and you live.
Answer now.
Unidentified(a.) pirata, this is O.P.A.S. Tynan.
We have target lock.
Shut down your drive. Prepare to be boarded.
Comply, or we will be forced(被迫) to fire.
You rabbiting, bossmang.
Fo(男名男子名) da(爸爸) shasa.
Ready the grapple.
Radiation(辐射) spiking.
Evasive(规避) action!
They're dumping(倾倒) core!
What faction(派别) are you with?
It pay well?
Fo(男名男子名) kill your own...
fo da(爸爸) Inners?
Three UN supply ships(船舶) got hit on this trade route
in one month.
Who is ignoring(忽视) the truce?
The one that still fight for the Belt.
Guess you the Inners' good little koyo now.
Content for the table scraps.
They keep Belters out of the Ring
so they find the gold first,
leave us with dirt.
And you help them.
Good little koyo.
Rocinante, you are entering(进入) the Ring Blockade(封锁) Zone.
Please transmit(传送) your access code.
Roger that.
There you go, partner.
Code received(接收) and verified.
You're clear for transit.
It's nice to know Martians(火星人)
have to go through this as well.
Yeah, but they get to train for years(年) in one G.(G.)
- How am I doing? - Good.
Bone density, muscle mass, heart-lung(心肺) capacity all up.
They send a mining(采矿) company
- under the name of science... - You need a break?
...to steal our land,
the legitimate(合法) claim of our people.
They call Belters terrorists(恐怖分子)
to strip us of our rights.
We all lost family on Ganymede(木卫三)
because of the Inners' war.
- Yeah. - Ilus is(现在) our home now,
and we will not be driven(驱动) out again.
Yeah.
Keep going.
Oye, Nagata.
What are you doing here?
Is the universe about to end again?
Did you think I'd miss a chance
to talk to you in real time?
Good to see you, kopeng.
A bit of a surprise to be seen.
The Inners don't shoot us to pieces(碎片) with their railguns.
We don't nuke(核武器) the Ring.
One big happy family now, I guess.
You've been(一直) busy, eh?
Over 40(40) Ring comm(通信) relays(继电器) installed(安装) to date, I gather.
Forty-two, which means only 1,331 to go.
With Medina(麦地那) Station the hub(中心) of it all.
It's a good command.
Only gas station on the new frontier.
We're putting(推杆) in a souvenir(纪念品) shop.
Be a lot of business after the blockade(封锁) lifts.
- How is your back? - Only hurts(伤害) when I move.
Which means nerves(神经) are regrowing, so that's(没错) good.
You're bound for Ilus.
That's(没错) right.
With James Holden(霍尔顿) on the gunship.
You're going to get the Belters off that planet.
We're not going to evict(驱逐) anyone.
We're going to make sure it's safe.
Safe?
You hear how many of those refugees(难民)
died(死亡) trying(尝试) to adapt?
A lot of them had to go back up to orbit.
They were foolish(愚蠢) to think they could live there.
It's not foolish(愚蠢) to want free air
and free water and a home for their children.
We are creatures(生物) of space.
In two generations, their children(孩子) will be Inners.
They won't(不会) even remember what they were.
Everyone should have the right to decide for themselves.
Of course.
Xalte to sif, Camina.
Dewe(德威) fasi, Nagata.
We won't(不会) be able to assess how badly the Belters
have contaminated(污染) the atmosphere(大气)
until we've(我们已经) actually been(一直) on the planet,
but once you're there, I'm hoping(希望) we can
convince them of the need to limit the damage.
I'm looking(看) forward to working with you, Captain.
We'll see you on New Terra.
We're through the Ring.
Be on Ilus in a few weeks. Then what?(什么？)
I'll(我会) let you know.
Thanks for the ride.
What...what are we supposed... Wait!
Got something you want to say to me, sailor?
Can I...
Can I buy you another beer?
Got RIF'd about six months(月) back.
They told(告诉) our whole unit, "Hey, thanks for the memories.
You're all civilians(平民) now."
Had a promotion(推广) coming(来了) up too.
That's(没错) the shit(该死) end of the stick.
You should know.
I watched(观察) your hearing on the feed.
You could've saved(保存) your benefits(福利) if you signed(签字的)
that statement they were waving(挥手) in front of you.
I'm sure it was good entertainment(娱乐).
- But you wouldn't. - I stand by what I did,
and I can live with the fallout.
That's(没错) what a Marine does.
First they order you to lie.
Then they strip you of your pension,
your skin, when you put honor first.
And he doesn't bitch(婊子) and whine(哀号) when the chips(薯条) are down.
He goes to the VA, gets(得到) a regular job...
I'm there every goddamn(该死的) day waiting(等待) in line.
The problem is, you've(你有) got too much time to think.
It's making(制造) you crazy.
Crazy?
Me crazy?
You look like you're about ready to vent(发泄)
someone's skull(颅骨) for looking(看) at you the wrong way.
You're not exactly the poster(海报) girl for mental health.
I didn't vent(发泄) yours.
Oh, bleeding(流血) heart.
Let me ask you something.
You were inside that Ring station.
What did you see?
Nothing that would make sense,
except a bunch of people killing(杀) each other
to control something they didn't even understand.
Tell you what, sailor.
Hang on to that uniform. Keep in tip-top.
You can be damn(该死的) sure there are plenty more wars(战争) coming.
Beltalowda would be wise to ask,
if now we kill our own on order of the Inners,
is this peace worth the price?
The OPA does not speak for all.
And those who stand with Fred(弗雷德) Johnson
and Anderson(安德森) Dawes(道斯) should bear in mind
the inevitable(必然) fate of wellwalla and collaborators(合作者).
Tynan, you're entering(进入) the Ring Blockade(封锁) Zone.
Please transmit(传送) your access code.
Tynan, no entry to the Ring is permitted(允许的)
without proper authorization(授权).
Transmit(传输) your access code immediately.
Bossmang, they target-lock us.
Tynan, this is your final warning.
Ah, give it to them.
Code verified.
Tynan, you're cleared(清除) for the Ring.
- Ashford. - What?(什么？)
We have enough problems(问题) already
without you agitating(搅动) the Inners.
Well, they like humiliating(羞辱的) us.
It's bad enough I have to play cop(警察) to protect their haulers.
- We have a treaty(条约). - Worth what to the Belt?
We'll find out, keya? You have to trust your gut.
Well, the last time I did that,
it didn't work out so well, did it?
We were all flying(飞行) blind, Pampaw.
Yeah, well, me more than you.
Only because my friend had a boyfriend(男朋友)
with an imaginary(想象的) friend
who told(告诉) us how to power that station down.
And I thought he was a madman.
But he...he turns(转弯) out to be a prophet.
It's possible to be both.
Why'd I let you talk me into this?
Are(是吗) you kidding?
First scientists(科学家) ever to study a whole new biome.
We're making(制造) history.
Maybe you will.
This planet has no geological(地质) activity.
And isn't(不是) that amazing?
I was with the Hygeia(女名女子名) group
when we found some Belters
squatting(蹲) on a rock with a billion in platinum(白金) ore(矿石)
- that we had the charter(租船合同) for. - How'd that go?
We gave(给) them a percentage(百分比) of the take, 300K,
topped(顶端) off their water tanks, sent(发送) them on their way.
You got off cheap.
Yeah, the company called(叫) it a win.
Well, let's(让我们) hope it's that easy here.
Yeah, we've(我们已经) got a legal charter(宪章) from the UN and Mars, so...
You think the OPA(管理局) give a shit(该死) about that?
No, I do not.
Lighten(放轻松) up, Fayez.
You're about to be famous.
Bet the rocks(岩石) down here look just like the ones(一个) back home.
Well, I'll name a new bug(虫子) after you.
Hold tight!
There's(有的) one over here!
Give me the mask!
It's okay. Come here.
Twenty-three(二十三) of our people are dead,
including the mission commander
and the ship's physician.
The heavy lift shuttle(穿梭) was destroyed,
along with most of the expedition's(远征) supplies.
Security Chief Murtry refused(拒绝) evacuation(疏散)
and is(现在) now in operational(操作的) command of the expedition(远征).
Cause of the crash is currently unknown.
The Belters are providing(提供) what aid they can
but hasten(催促) to add the company had no right
to land in the first place.
It could have been(一直) an accident or attack
or something much worse.
The story is already metastasizing(转移) on newsfeeds.
Just get yourself to Ilus, do your job,
and let RCE do theirs.
The Belters will try to enlist(争取) you to their cause.
Holden, do not put your dick(鸡巴) in it.
It's fucked enough already.
It's good advice.
Cap, test fire lined(衬里) up.
Fire at will.
Take that, blue goo.
Belte hero.
You na(好吧) kang(康) let them take us from our land.
This our home.
This our land, huh? This Belter land.
Nobody's doing anything to anybody.
We're here to help.
Welcome. Carol(卡罗尔) Chiwewe.
I'm the administrator(管理人) of the settlement(殖民地).
- Jim Holden. - Captain Holden.
Chief Murtry. Welcome to New Terra.
Come with me.(我。) I'll give you the lay of the land.
Good to meet you.
Hey, you here fo help us or help them?
All right, all right, easy there, partner.
Traitors!
Traitor. Traitor.
Traitor!
Everybody put your guns(枪) down now!
- Amos, you too. - Him first.
You've got two seconds.
Pashang, you got one.
What the fuck is that?
Take cover!
You okay?
Amos.
Son of a bitch.
- Jesus. - What the fuck was that?
Hey, you okay?